JUSTIN WEBB

WEB DEVELOPER ♥ THOMPSONVILLE,IL, 62890, UNITED STATES 6186632429

• DETAILS •

22689 Corinth Rd Thompsonville,IL, 62890 United States 6186632429

justinwebbmain@gmail.com

· LINKS ·

Portfolio Website

SKILLS

JavaScript

HTML/CSS

React

Bootstrap

NodeJs

GitHub

PROFILE

Attended a coding boot camp provided by the University of California. Once completing that course, I began developing my own personal projects and working freelance utilizing the skills I learned. With my knowledge and experience I would be a welcomed asset to any team.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Freelance Web Developer

November 2022 — Present

- Provided my services for free to local businesses in order to gain real world development experience
- Planned, developed, tested, deployed, and maintained web applications.
- Worked to assess competing websites in regards to content, look, and feel.
- Effectively translated client requirements into application designs and system requirements.

Geek Squad Agent at Geek Squad, Lake Geneva

January 2017 — January 2019

- Led a team in the redesign of the store's network infrastructure
- Held the highest customer satisfaction score in our state through the entirety of my employment
- Utilized senior employees knowledge in order to grow my own knowledge so i could be of better service to our clients
- Researched problems to find fast and effective solutions for clients

EDUCATION

University of California, Berkeley, Certification of Completion Full Stack Web Development, San Francisco

May 2019 — December 2019

- Acquired full stack skill set which includes HTML/CSS/React/NodeJs
- · Completed several full stack projects independently
- Led a team in the completion of a keystone project at the end of the course
- · Leveraged my time with mentors in order to grow my knowledge and skills
- Earned a certification of completion after 6 months

Grayslake North High School

- Attended Tech Campus program that was associated with the College of Lake County that specialized in computer support services
- · Assisted IT department with network and hardware maintenance

■ REFERENCES

Aaron Pierce Software Engineer/Mentor from Silverworks Solutions pierceaaron424@gmail.com · 2247724917

Dan Krajewski Software Engineer/Mentor from Silverworks Solutions danieljkrajewski@gmail.com · 8479178227